{
    "subject": "resource/Desperate_Teenage_Lovedolls",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "Hilary Rubens",
    "human_readable": "Desperate Teenage Lovedolls stars Hilary Rubens.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.865500271320343,
            "question": "Who stars in the movie Desperate Teenage Lovedolls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6747267246246338,
            "question": "What is the plot of Desperate Teenage Lovedolls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6130485534667969,
            "question": "What genre is Desperate Teenage Lovedolls likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5739135146141052,
            "question": "Do you know the director of Desperate Teenage Lovedolls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5719166398048401,
            "question": "Where was Desperate Teenage Lovedolls filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5699853897094727,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie starring Hilary Rubens?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5638270974159241,
            "question": "Is Hilary Rubens an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5449433922767639,
            "question": "What year was Desperate Teenage Lovedolls released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4559056758880615,
            "question": "Can you tell me about another movie starring Hilary Rubens?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.439674973487854,
            "question": "Is there a trailer for Desperate Teenage Lovedolls available online?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Desperate Teenage Lovedolls stars Hilary Rubens.",
            "html": "dbpedia_94_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about another movie starring Hilary Rubens?",
            "html": "dbpedia_94_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Desperate Teenage Lovedolls released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_94_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Hilary Rubens an actress?",
            "html": "dbpedia_94_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_94_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_94_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_94_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_94_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_94_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_94_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_94_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_94_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_94_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_94_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Desperate Teenage Lovedolls is a film directed by David Markey and starring Jennifer Schwartz, Hilary Rubens, Janet Housden. There is no specific mention of Pat Frank, Elisabeth Domitien, or Camilo Jos\u00e9 Cela in the provided context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Hilary Rubens starred in \"Desperate Teenage Lovedolls,\" so the statement \"Desperate Teenage Lovedolls stars Hilary Rubens\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}